Rick Whitesell Record Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. 10" Discs, 1; 15 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 24 Folders: 1.10.1 - 1.10.1090
  - Bull Moose Jackson&His Buffalo Bearcats, Record Label: King (565, Box 13)
    - I Love You Yes I Do, 2
  - Bull Moose Jackson&His Buffalo Bearcats, Record Label: King (566, Box 13)
    - I Want A Bowlegged Woman, 1
    - All My Love Belongs To You, 2
  - Bull Moose Jackson&His Buffalo Bearcats, Record Label: King (567, Box 13)
    - I Can't Go On Without You, 1
    - Fare Thee Well, Deacon Jones, 2
  - Delores Jackson&The Cabin Boys, Record Label: Decca (568, Box 13)
    - Cloudy, 1
    - Carelessly, 2
  - Mahalia Jackson, Record Label: Apollo (569, Box 13)
    - Get Away Jordon, 1
    - I Gave Up Everything To Follow Him, 2
  - Mahalia Jackson, Record Label: Apollo (570, Box 13)
    - I Have A Friend, 1
    - There's Not A Friend Like Jesus, 2
  - Rudy Jackson and The Mel-O-Aries, Record Label: R&B (571, Box 13)
    - Enfold me, 1
    - I'm Crying, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (572, Box 13)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (573, Box 13)
  - Elmer James, Record Label: Trumpet (574, Box 13)
    - Gonna Find My Baby, 1
    - Make A Little Love With Me, 2
  - Elmore James&His Broom Dusters, Record Label: Flair (575, Box 13)
    - Make A Little Love, 1
    - Can't Stop Lovin, 2
  - Elmore James&His Broom Dusters, Record Label: Flair (576, Box 13)
    - Hawaiian Boogie, 1
    - Early In The Morning, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (577, Box 13)
  - The Jewels, Record Label: Imperial (578, Box 13)
    - How, 1
    - Rickety Rock, 2
  - Bill Johnson, Record Label: Columbia (579, Box 13)
    - Doot Doot Dow, 1
    - I Don't Want Nobody (To Have My Love But You), 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (581, Box 13)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (582, Box 13)
  - Lonnie Johnson, Record Label: King (583, Box 13)
    - Darlin', 1
    - Seven Long Days, 2
  - Al Jolson - Four Record Set Record 1, Record Label: Decca (584, Box 13)
    - April Showers, 1
    - Swanee, 2
  - Al Jolson - Four Record Set Record 2, Record Label: Decca (585, Box 13)
    - California, Here I Come, 1
    - Rock A Bye Your Baby With A Dizie Melody, 2
  - Al Jolson - Four Record Set Record 3, Record Label: Decca (586, Box 13)
    - Sonny Boy, 1
    - My Mammy, 2
  - Al Jolson - Four Record Set Record 4, Record Label: Decca (10.587, Box 13)
    - Ma Blushin' Rosie, 1
    - You Made Me Love You, 2
  - Albinia Jones with Don Byas' Swing Seven, Record Label: National (588, Box 13)
    - Albinia's Blues, 1
    - Salty Papa Blues, 2
  - Jones Boys Sing Band with Otis Rene, Record Label: Decca (589, Box 13)
    - Sleepy Time In Hawaii, 1
    - Jones Boys Sing Band Pickin' A Rib, 2
  - The Jones Brothers, Record Label: Majestic (590, Box 13)
    - Them There Eyes, 1
  - Louis Jordan&His Tympany Five A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Decca (591, Box 13)
    - Beware, 1
    - Don't Let The Sun Catch You Cryin', 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (592, Box 13)
  - Louis Jordan&His Tympany Five, Record Label: Decca (593, Box 13)
    - If It's Love You Want Baby, That's Me, 1
    - Ain't That Just Like A Woman (They'll Do it Every Time), 2
  - Louis Jordan&His Tympany Five, Record Label: Decca (594, Box 13)
    - Let The Good Times Roll, 1
    - Ain't Nobody Here But Us Chickens, 2
  - Louis Jordan&His Tympany Five, Record Label: Decca (595, Box 13)
    - Texas And Pacific, 1
    - I Like 'Em Fat Like That, 2
  - Louis Jordan&His Tympany Five, Record Label: Decca (596, Box 13)
    - G.I. Jive, 1
    - Is You Is Or Is You Ain't (my Baby), 2
  - The Jubalaires, Record Label: Capitol (597, Box 14)
    - Mene Mene Teckel, 1
    - Somebody Broke My Dolly, 2
  - The Jubalaires, Record Label: Capitol (598, Box 14)
    - That Old Piano Blues, 1
    - A Dream Is A Wish Your Heart Makes, 2
  - The Jubalaires, Record Label: Decca (599, Box 14)
    - Before This Time Another Year, 1
    - When It's All Over But The Shoutin', 2
  - The Jubalaires, Record Label: Queen (600, Box 14)
    - Jube's Blues, 1
    - I've Waited All My Life For You, 2
  - The Original Jubalaires, Record Label: Crown (601, Box 14)
    - Waiting All My Life For You, 1
    - Dreaming Of The Ladies In The Moon, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (602, Box 14)
  - Jubilee Singers, Record Label: Bluebird (603, Box 14)
    - O Mary, Don't You Weep, 1
    - Couldn't Hear Nobody Pray, 2
  - The Jubileers, Record Label: Bluebird (604, Box 14)
    - Boogie Woogie Johnson, 1
    - The Right String But The Wrong Yoyo, 2
  - Little Junior's Blue Flames, Record Label: (605, Box 14)
    - Love My Baby, 1
    - Mystery Train, 2
  - "Tiny" Kennedy, Record Label: Trumpet (606, Box 14)
    - Blues Disease, 1
    - Don't Lay This Job On Me, 2
  - "Tiny" Kennedy, Record Label: Trumpet (607, Box 14)
    - Strange Kind Of Feeling, 1
    - Early In The Morning, Baby, 2
  - Bill Kenny (Mr. Ink Spot), Record Label: Vik (608, Box 14)
    - Now You Say You Care - Shuffle, 1
    - Now You Say You Care - Ballad, 2
  - Bill Kenny (Of The Ink Spots) and The Song Spinners (dual listed), Record Label: Decca (609, Box 14)
    - The Gentle Carpenter of Bethlehem, 1
    - Stubby&The Buccaneers - The Gentle Carpenter of Bethlehem, 2
  - The Kings featuring Bobby Hill, Record Label: Jax (610, Box 14)
    - Baby Be There, 1
    - You Made Me Cry, 2
  - Andy Kirk&His Orchestra and The Jubalaires, Record Label: Decca (611, Box 14)
    - I'm So Lonesome I Could Cry, 1
    - I Don't Know What I'd Do Without You, 2
  - Eartha Kitt, Record Label: RCA Victor (612, Box 14)
    - I Wanna Be Evil, 1
    - C'Est Si Bon, 2
    - Angelitos Negros, 3
    - Avril Au Portugal, 4
    - Uska Dara, 5
    - African Lullaby, 6
    - Mountain High - Valley Low, 7
    - Lilac Wine, 8
  - Marie Knight, Record Label: Decca (613, Box 14)
    - Calvary, 1
    - God Spoke To Me, 2
  - Gene Krupa And His Orchestra, Record Label: Columbia (614, Box 14)
    - Boogie Blues, 1
    - Lover, 2
  - Kay Kyser&His Orchestra, Record Label: Columbia (615, Box 14)
    - Jingle Jangle Jingle, 1
    - He Wears A Pair Of Silver Wings, 2
  - Herb Lance, Record Label: Sittin' in With (616, Box 14)
    - Stardust, 1
    - Begin The Beguine, 2
  - Herb Lance, Record Label: Sittin' in With (617, Box 14)
    - That Lucky Old Sun, 1
    - If My Dream Would Come True, 2
  - The Lancers, Record Label: Trend (618, Box 14)
    - Peggy O'Neil, 1
    - Stop Chasin' Me Baby, 2
  - Georgia Lane With Orchestra (dual listed), Record Label: Central (619, Box 14)
    - Co-Wee Mr. Jeff (Please Be Yourself), 1
    - Emmett Hobson and The Rag-Muffins Looka Here, Mattie Bee, 2
  - Sam Lanin's Dance Ensemble, Record Label: Hit of the Week (620, Box 14)
    - Hello! Beautiful!, 1
  - Frankie Laine, Record Label: Mercury (621, Box 14)
    - Black Lace, 1
    - The Cry Of The Wild Goose, 2
  - Frankie Laine, Record Label: Mercury (622, Box 14)
    - That Lucky Old Sun, 1
    - I Get Sentimental Over Nothing, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (623, Box 14)
  - The Larks, Record Label: Lloyds (624, Box 14)
    - Margie, 1
    - Rockin' In The Rocket Room, 2
  - Leo And His Trio, Record Label: Intro (625, Box 14)
    - Anytime, 1
    - Silver Spurs, 2
  - Jimmy "Baby Face" Lewis&His Band, Record Label: Atlantic (626, Box 14)
    - Mailman Blues, 1
    - I'm So Good To You (Pretty Baby), 2
  - Joe Liggins&His Honeydrippers, Record Label: Exclusive (627, Box 14)
    - The Blues, 1
    - Blow Mr. Jackson, 2
  - Lightnin' Slim, Record Label: Excello (628, Box 14)
    - Have Your Way, 1
    - Bad Luck And Trouble, 2
  - Guy Lombardo&His Royal Canadians, Record Label: Decca (629, Box 14)
    - Four Record Set - Missing One Record
    - Make Believe, 1
    - I'm Always Chasing Rainbows, 2
  - Guy Lombardo&His Royal Canadians, Record Label: Decca (630, Box 14)
    - Four Record Set
    - Smoke Gets In Your Eyes, 1
    - The Very Thought Of You, 2
  - Guy Lombardo&His Royal Canadians, Record Label: Decca (631, Box 14)
    - Four Record Set
    - At Dawning, 1
    - When Day Is Done, 2
  - Guy Lombardo&His Royal Canadians and The Andres Sisters, Record Label: Decca (632, Box 14)
    - Jolly Fella Tarantella (The Organ Grinder's Song), 1
    - Stars Are The Windows Of Heaven, 2
  - Joe Hill Louis, Record Label: Checker (633, Box 14)
    - Dorothy Mae, 1
    - When I Am Gone, 2
  - Willie Love&The Three Aces, Record Label: Trumpet (634, Box 14)
    - Way Back, 1
    - Shout, Brother, Shout, 2
  - Willie Love&The Three Aces, Record Label: Trumpet (635, Box 14)
    - V-8 Ford, 1
    - Nelson Street Blues, 2
  - Willie Love&His Three Aces, Record Label: Trumpet (636, Box 14)
    - My Own Boogie, 1
    - Everybody's Fishing, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (637, Box 14)
  - Willie Love&His Three Aces, Record Label: Trumpet (638, Box 14)
    - Little Car Blues, 1
    - Take It Easy, Baby, 2
  - Willie Love&His Three Aces, Record Label: Trumpet (639, Box 14)
    - Shady Lane Blues, 1
    - 21 Minutes To Nine, 2
  - Willie Love&His Three Aces, Record Label: Trumpet (640, Box 14)
    - Vanity Dresser Boogie, 1
    - Seventy Four Blues, 2
  - Jimmie Lunceford&His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (641, Box 14)
    - Coquette, 1
    - For Dancers Only, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (642, Box 14)
  - Jimmie Lunceford&His Orchestra, Record Label: Vocalion (643, Box 14)
    - Cheatin' On Me, 1
    - 'Taint What You Do (It's The Way You Do It), 2
  - Jimmie Lanceford&His Orchestra, Record Label: Bluebird (644, Box 14)
    - Jazznocrazy, 1
    - White Heat, 2
  - Nellie Lutcher&Her Rhythm, Record Label: Capitol (645, Box 14)
    - He's A Real Gone Guy, 1
    - Let Me Love You Tonight, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (646, Box 15)
  - Brownie McGhee (Blind Boy Fuller #2), Record Label: OKeh (647, Box 15)
    - Workingman's Blues, 1
    - Step It Up And Go No. 2, 2
  - Brownie McGhee, Record Label: Conqueror (648, Box 15)
    - ? worn label - not readable, 1
    - ? worn label - not readable, 2
  - Howard McGhee&His Orchestra (dual listed), Record Label: Modern Music (649, Box 15)
    - 11:45 Swing, 1
    - Pearl Traylor with Howard McGhee&His Orchestra - Play Boy Blues, 2
  - Red McKenzie with The Spirits Of Rhythm, Record Label: Decca (650, Box 15)
    - From Monday On, 1
    - Way Down Yonder In New Orleans, 2
  - Clyde McPhatter, Record Label: Atlantic (651, Box 15)
    - Seven Days, 1
    - I'm Not Worthy Of You, 2
  - Johnny Maddox with The Rhythm Masters, Record Label: Dot (652, Box 15)
    - Near you, 1
    - Johnny Maddox Boogie, 2
  - Silvana Mangano, Record Label: MGM (653, Box 15)
    - Anna, 1
    - I Loved You, 2
  - Manhattan Paul and The Three Riffs, Record Label: Atlantic (654, Box 15)
    - Hard Ridin' Mama, 1
    - I Wish I Didn't Love You So, 2
  - Gloria Mann with The Carter Rays, Record Label: Jubilee (655, Box 15)
    - Love-Me-Boys, 1
    - Goodnight Sweetheart Goodnight, 2
  - The Marigolds, Record Label: Excello (656, Box 15)
    - Why Don't You, 1
    - Rollin' Stone, 2
  - The Marshall Brothers, Record Label: Savoy (657, Box 15)
    - Just A Poor Boy In Love, 1
    - Why Make A Fool Out Of Me, 2
  - The Roberta Martin Singers, Record Label: Savoy (658, Box 15)
    - Sinner Man, Where You Gonna Run To, 1
    - Nothing But A God, 2
  - The Marylanders, Record Label: Jubilee (659, Box 15)
    - Sittin' By The River, 1
    - I'm A Sentimental Fool, 2
  - Big Maybelle, Record Label: OKeh (660, Box 15)
    - My Big Mistake, 1
    - I'm Getting 'Long Alright, 2
  - Big Maybelle, Record Label: Okeh (661, Box 15)
    - I've Got A Feelin', 1
    - You'll Never Know, 2
  - Big Maybelle, Record Label: Okeh (662, Box 15)
    - Ain't No Use, 1
    - Don't Leave Poor Me, 2
  - The Mellows, Record Label: Jay-Dee (663, Box 15)
    - I Still Care, 1
    - I Was A Fool To Let You Go, 2
  - Memphis Slim&The Houserockers, Record Label: Premium (664, Box 15)
    - Flock Rocker, 1
    - I Guess I'm A Fool, 2
  - Wally Mercer, Record Label: Trumpet (665, Box 15)
    - Too Old To Get Married (Too Young To Settle Down), 1
    - If You Don't Mean Business, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (666, Box 15)
  - The Midnights, Record Label: Music City (667, Box 15)
    - Hear My Plea, 1
    - Annie Pulled a Hum-Bug, 2
  - The Midnights, Record Label: Music City (668, Box 15)
    - She Left Me, 1
    - Cheating On Me, 2
  - Mills Brothers Famous Barber Shop Ballads, Record Label: Decca (669, Box 15)
    - 4 record set - missing 1 record
    - Till We Meet Again, 1
    - Honey, Dat I Love So Well, 2
  - Mills Brothers Famous Barber Shop Ballads, Record Label: Decca (670, Box 15)
    - Sweet Genevieve, 1
    - If I Had My Way, 2
  - Mills Brothers Famous Barber Shop Ballads, Record Label: Decca (671, Box 15)
    - Long Long Ago, 1
    - Love's Old Sweet Song, 2
  - Mills Brothers Famous Barber Shop Ballads - Volume 1, Record Label: Decca (672, Box 15)
    - You Tell Me Your Dream, I'll Tell You Mine, 1
    - Sweet Adeline, 2
    - My Gal Sal, 3
    - Just A Dream Of You, Dear, 4
    - Meet Me Tonight in Dreamland, 5
    - Can't You Hear Me Callin' Caroline, 6
    - Way Down Home, 7
    - When You Were Sweet Sixteen, 8
  - Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (673, Box 15)
    - Miss Otis Regrets (She's Unable To Lunch Today), 1
    - Old Fashioned Love, 2
  - Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (674, Box 15)
    - Don't Be Afraid To Tell Your Mother, 1
    - That's The Reason (I'm Not Pleasin' You), 2
  - Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (675, Box 15)
    - Delilah, 1
    - The Window Washer Man, 2
  - The Mills Brothers A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Decca (676, Box 15)
    - I Guess I'll Get The Papers (And Go Home), 1
    - Too Many Irons In The Fire, 2
  - The Mills Brothers A, B, C,&D, Record Label: 4 copies Decca (677, Box 15)
    - Paper Doll, 1
    - I'll Be Around, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (678, Box 15)
    - Pretty Butterfly, 1
    - Don't Let Me Dream, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (679, Box 15)
    - Sixty Seconds Got Together, 1
    - Julius Caesar, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (680, Box 15)
    - Single Saddle, 1
    - Gather Your Dreams, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (681, Box 15)
    - Why Fight The Feeling, 1
    - The Tunnel Of Love, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (682, Box 15)
    - I'm The Guy, 1
    - Ninety-Eight Cents, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (683, Box 15)
    - Manana, 1
    - I Wish I Knew The Name (Of The Girl Of My Dreams), 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (684, Box 15)
    - After You, 1
    - You Never Miss The Water Till The Well Runs Dry, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (685, Box 15)
    - I'm Happy Being Me, 1
    - Words (That Are Breaking My Heart), 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (686, Box 15)
    - Gloria, 1
    - I Want To Be The Only One, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (687, Box 15)
    - I'll Never Be Without A Dream (As Long As I Have You), 1
    - Two Blocks Down... Turn To The Left (On The Right Hand Of The Street), 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (688A, Box 16)
    - Sweet Adeline, 1
    - You Tell Me Your Dreams I'll Tell You Mine, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (689, Box 16)
    - If It's True, 1
    - The Very Thought Of You, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (690, Box 16)
    - I Don't Know Enough About You, 1
    - I Don't Know Enough About You, 2
  - The Mills Brothers A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Decca (691, Box 16)
    - Oh! My Achin' Heart, 1
    - What You Don't Know Won't Hurt You, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (692, Box 16)
    - Daddy's Little Girl, 1
    - If I Live To Be A Hundred, 2
  - The Mills Brothers A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Decca (693, Box 16)
    - Till Then, 1
    - You Always Hurt The One You Love, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (694, Box 16)
    - Baby Don't Be Mad At Me, 1
    - I Couldn't Call My Baby (Anything But Baby), 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (695, Box 16)
    - A Carnival In Venice, 1
    - Go In And Out The Window, 2
  - The Mills Brothers A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Decca (696, Box 16)
    - My Gal Sal, 1
    - Just A Dream Of You, Dear, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (697, Box 16)
    - Old Black Joe, 1
    - Swanee River, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (698, Box 16)
    - Dreamsville, Ohio, 1
    - Beyond The Stars, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (699, Box 16)
    - S-H-I-N-E, 1
    - Love Is Fun, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (700, Box 16)
    - Don't Be A Baby, Baby, 1
    - Never Make A Promise In Vain, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (701, Box 16)
    - Meet Me Tonight In Dreamland, 1
    - Can't You Hear Me Callin', Caroline, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (702, Box 16)
    - On A Chinese Honeymoon, 1
    - Someday (You'll Want Me To Want You), 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (703, Box 16)
    - Moonlight Bay, 1
    - On The Banks Of The Wabash (Far Away), 2
  - The Mills Brothers A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Decca (704, Box 16)
    - I Wish, 1
    - Put Another Chair At The Table, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (705, Box 16)
    - Since We Fell Out Of Love, 1
    - In The Shade Of The Old Apple Tree, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (706A, Box 16)
    - Way Down Home, 1
    - When You Were Sweet Sixteen, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (706B, Box 16)
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (707, Box 16)
    - Darling Nelly Gray, 1
    - Break The News To Mother, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (708, Box 16)
    - Out Of Love, 1
    - Lora-Belle Lee, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (709, Box 16)
    - Love Lies, 1
    - Be My Life's Companion, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (710, Box 16)
    - The Bells Of San Raguel, 1
    - I Guess I'll Be On My Way, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (711, Box 16)
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Decca (712, Box 16)
    - Will There Be Any Stars?, 1
    - Now The Day Is Over, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (713, Box 16)
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (714, Box 16)
    - Rockin' Chair, 1
    - Good-bye Blues, 2
  - The Mills Brothers A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Brunswick (715, Box 16)
    - Tiger Rag, 1
    - Nobody's Sweetheart, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (716, Box 16)
    - The Old Man Of The Mountain, 1
    - Bugle Call Rag, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (717, Box 16)
    - Git Along, 1
    - Dirt Dishin' Daisy, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (718, Box 16)
    - It Don't Mean A Thing (If It Ain't Got That Swing), 1
    - Coney Island Washboard, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (719, Box 16)
    - St. Louis Blues, 1
    - Sweet Sue - Just You, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (720, Box 16)
    - Loveless Love, 1
    - Chinatown, My Chinatown, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (721, Box 16)
    - Sleepy Head, 1
    - Put On Your Old Grey Bonnet, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Brunswick (722, Box 16)
    - Jungle Fever, 1
    - I Found A New Baby, 2
  - The Mills Brothers A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Brunswick (723, Box 16)
    - You Rascal You, 1
    - Baby Won't You Please Come Home, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Oriole (724, Box 16)
    - I Found A New Baby, 1
    - Baby Won't You Please Come Home, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Melotone (725, Box 16)
    - Sleepy Head, 1
    - Jungle Fever, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Perfect (726, Box 17)
    - Dirt Dishin' Daisy, 1
    - Fiddlin' Joe, 2
  - The Mills Brothers, Record Label: Polydor (727, Box 17)
    - Nagasaki, 1
    - Lazy Bones, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (728, Box 17)
  - The Mills Brothers and Louis Armstrong, Record Label: Decca (729, Box 17)
    - Cherry, 1
    - Boog-It, 2
  - Mills Brothers with Benny Carter&His Orchestra, Record Label: 2 copies Decca (730, Box 17)
    - By The Watermelon Vine, Lindy Lou, 1
    - Benny Carter&His Orchestra I've Been In Love Before, 2
  - Mills Brothers and Ella Fitzgerald, Record Label: Decca (731, Box 17)
    - Big Boy Blue, 1
    - Dedicated To You, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (732, Box 17)
  - Mills Brothers with Sly Oliver&His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (733, Box 17)
    - She Was Five and He Was Ten, 1
    - The Jones Boys, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (734, Box 17)
  - Glenn Miller&His Orchestra, Record Label: RCA Victor (735, Box 17)
    - Elmer's Tune, 1
    - Juke Box Saturday Night, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (736, Box 17)
  - Glenn Miller&His Orchestra, Record Label: RCA Victor (737, Box 17)
    - Pennsylvania Six-Five Thousand, 1
    - Star Dust, 2
  - Glenn Miller&His Orchestra, Record Label: Bluebird (738, Box 17)
    - Slip Horn Jive, 1
    - Guess I'll Go Back Home, 2
  - Glenn Miller&His Orchestra, Record Label: RCA Victor (739, Box 17)
    - Tuxedo Junction, 1
    - In The Mood, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (740, Box 17)
  - Lucky Millinder&His Orchestra, Record Label: King (741, Box 17)
    - My Little Baby, 1
    - Let It Roll Again, 2
  - Lucky Millinder&His Orchestra, Record Label: King (742, Box 17)
    - Bongo Boogie, 1
    - I'm Waiting Just For You, 2
  - Lucky Millinder&His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (743, Box 17)
    - Shipyard Social Function, 1
    - Who Threw The Whiskey In The Well, 2
  - Mitchell's Christian Singers, Record Label: Conqueror (744, Box 17)
    - How About You?, 1
    - What Are They Doing In Heaven?, 2
  - Bobby Mitchell&The Toppers, Record Label: Imperial (745, Box 17)
    - 4 x 11 = 44, 1
    - One Friday Morning, 2
  - Mitzi Mars, Record Label: Checker (746, Box 17)
    - I'm Glad, 1
    - Roll 'Em, 2
  - Monarch Jazz Quartet, Record Label: OKeh (747, Box 17)
    - Four Or Five Times, 1
    - What's The Matter Now?, 2
  - Bill Monroe&The Blue Grass Boys, Record Label: Columbia (748, Box 17)
    - Goodbye Old Pal, 1
    - Blue Moon Of Kentucky, 2
  - Vaughn Monroe Vaughn Monroe Plays Cole Porter For Dancing, Record Label: RCA Victor (749, Box 17)
    - So In Love, 1
    - Easy To Love, 2
    - Don't Fence Me In, 3
    - What Is This Thing Called Love?, 4
    - I Get A Kick Out Of You, 5
    - I Concentrate On You, 6
  - The Phil Moore Four, Record Label: 2 copies Victor (751, Box 17)
    - A Little On The Lonely Side, 1
    - My Dreams Are Getting Better All The Time, 2
  - Rocky Morgan's Triple R Boys, Record Label: Modern Hollywood (752, Box 17)
    - Turn That Gun Around, 1
    - Hen Peckin Mama, 2
  - Russ Morgan&His Orchestra, Record Label: Decca (753, Box 17)
    - So Long, 1
    - What's The Matter With Me, 2
  - Joe Morris&His Orchestra A&B, Record Label: 2 copies Atlantic (754, Box 17)
    - Come Back, Daddy, Daddy, 1
    - Anytime, Anyplace, Anywhere, 2
  - Joe Morris&His Orchestra, Record Label: Atlantic (755, Box 17)
    - Stormy Weather, 1
    - Don't Take Your Love Away From Me, 2
  - Joe Morris&His Orchestra, Record Label: Atlantic (76, Box 17)
    - Watch Out I Told You, 1
    - Faye Adams with Joe Morris&His Orchestra - Sweet Talk, 2
  - Joe Morrison&The Four Esquires, Record Label: Brunswick (757, Box 17)
    - I Lost My Heart, 1
    - Lazy Bones Gotta Job Now, 2
  - Mullen Brothers, Record Label: Tip Top (758, Box 17)
    - I've Just Heard From Heaven, 1
    - An Empty Mansion, 2
  - Moon Mullican, Record Label: King (759, Box 17)
    - I Was Sorta Wonderin', 1
    - The Leaves Mustn't Fall, 2
  - Jimmy Nelson&The Peter Rabbit Trio, Record Label: RPM (760, Box 17)
    - "T" 99 Blues, 1
    - Rain Drop Blues, 2